{"id":"picture_description_1","collection":"cardCollections","data":{"title":"Picture: Family Breakfast","tags":["Speaking","Descriptions"],"cardList":[{"front":"En esta imagen puedo ver ...","back":"In this picture I can see ..."},{"front":"(¿Quiénes?) Una familia asiática","back":"(who) an Asian family"},{"front":"(¿Qué están haciendo?) Desayunando","back":"(doing what) having breakfast"},{"front":"(¿Dónde?) En su jardín","back":"(where) in their garden"},{"front":"(¿Cuándo?) Y es un bonito día soleado","back":"(when) And it's a beautiful sunny day"},{"front":"(Descripción general) Hay cinco personas en la imagen, tres de ellas sentadas alrededor de una mesa y dos de pie","back":"(general description) There are five people in the picture, three of them are sitting around a table and two of them are standing up"},{"front":"(¿Cómo se sienten?) Todos parecen muy felices","back":"(how do they feel) They all seem very happy"},{"front":"En la mesa hay muchos platos con comida y algunos vasos con zumo de naranja","back":"On the table, there are plenty of dishes with food and some glasses with orange juice"},{"front":"También puedo ver una botella de agua a la izquierda","back":"I can also see a bottle of water on the left"},{"front":"(Especulación) El hombre del centro parece mayor que los demás, por lo que podría ser un abuelo","back":"(speculation) The man in the middle looks older than the others, so he might be a grandfather"},{"front":"(Especulación) y las otras personas podrían ser sus hijos y nietos","back":"(speculation) and the other people could be his children and grandchildren"},{"front":"(Conclusión) El hombre de la izquierda sostiene un regalo y la mujer de la derecha sostiene unas flores","back":"(conclusion) The man on the left is holding a present and the woman on the right is holding some flowers"},{"front":"Así que creo que podría ser el cumpleaños o aniversario de alguien, esto es probablemente el porque todos están tan felices","back":"(conclusion) so I believe it might be someone's birthday or anniversary, that's probably why they are all so happy"},{"front":"(Detalles menos relevantes) Debe ser verano o primavera porque hace mucho sol y toda la familia lleva ropa corta","back":"(less relevant details) It must be summer or spring because it's really sunny and the family are all wearing short leaves"},{"front":"Al fondo puedo ver un poco de hierba, algunos árboles y las casas de los vecinos","back":"In the background I can see some grass, a few trees and the neighbour's houses"}]}}